Kush Manocha

Key Account Manager at Bharti Airtel Limited

Experience

Key Account Manager at Bharti Airtel Limited December 2013 - Present (1 year 7 months)

- Relationship Management with Middle Management and Key- End Users of the account on a day to day basis for the given set of SME and ME accounts. Order entry, provisioning & management reporting. Carry VAS Targets- For products viz. Audio/ Video Conferencing, Blackberry, Data Cards, Vehicle Tracking. Carry 3 G Targets including Dongles, Mobility Revenue and Mobility Order Booking as well as retention of existing revenue. Carry Fixed Line OB and Fixed Line Revenue Generation as well as Retention of existing revenue. Co-ordinate with the cross functional teams internally- BSG, SMG(COPC), Administration Manager and Front Line sales.
- Customer loyalty management initiatives and the CRM activities for the account. Ensure the account business target achievement on: Order booking, Revenues, Collections, Coordination with Projects/Products/COPC to ensure meeting customer expectations on customer delivery.

Territory Sales Manager at Bharti Airtel Limited June 2012 - November 2013 (1 year 6 months)

- Accountable for SME Corporate Segment Business Development and New business development in Delhi and NCR Region. This involves B2B Telemedia sales, driven through channel partners in a given territory. Handling multiple channel partners and ensuring target completion, their training and development and giving them support. Tracking competitors' products and strategies in terms of features, benefits and cost and fine tuning of organization's sales and marketing strategies.
- Expertise in giving complete Business Solution offered by Bharti to all the new customers. Appointed a fleet of strong channel partner which are capable of doing data business. With mutual understanding, appointed quality manpower under each SI and make them productive for the company. Expertise in selling all data products of Bharti like ILL, MPLS, VOIP, Data Centre, VC and AC. To ensure working of channels as per standards and guidelines of Bharti Airtel Ltd. Ensuring customer service and satisfaction.

Summer Intern at Johnson & Johnson May 2011 - June 2011 (2 months)

Brand Neutrogena

Summary

An MBA from Amity Business School and having an experience of 3 years in corporate sales and Key Account Management/client servicing. Career Objective: To make a sound position in corporate world and work enthusiastically in a team to achieve goals of the organization with devotion and hard work. Soft Skills: Quick learner, Good Grasp on concepts, Keenness to learn, People's person, Empathetic, Effective communication skills, Responsible, Confident, Positive Attitude and Team Player.

Skills & Expertise

Corporate Sales Management

Team Management

Data Sales

Telemedia Products

Cross Selling

Channel Management

Channel Sales

Key Account Management

Languages

English

Hindi

Punjabi

French

Education

Amity Business School

Master of Business Administration (MBA), Marketing & Sales, 2010 - 2012

Grade: A

Activities and Societies: Vice Captain-ABS; Sports and cultural events; IMT-Ghaziabad sports event

Punjab Technical University

Bachelor of Technology (BTech), Information Technology, 2005 - 2009

Grade: A

Kush Manocha

Key Account Manager at Bharti Airtel Limited



Contact Kush on LinkedIn